http://www.lear.com/Site/Company/privacy.aspx

Company  /  Privacy
Overview History Vision & Values Leadership Newsroom COVID-19 Updates Idea Portal Resources Lear Student Innovation Challenge
Connect with Lear
To learn more about our products and capabilities, or to get in touch with a Lear representative, contact us today.
Contact us
Privacy
This document describes the policy of Lear Corporation (“Lear”), regarding information received about you during visits to our Web site. The amount and type of information received depends on how you use our site.
This Privacy Statement describes the ways in which Lear collects, holds and uses information about individuals who visit our Web site (“Personal Data”).
The data controller for processing your Personal Data within the meaning of data protection laws such as the General Data Protection Regulation is Lear Corporation, 21557 Telegraph Road, Southfield, MI 48033, USA/Phone: 1-248-447-1500 and E-Mail:
DataPrivacy@lear.com.
Collection of Personal Information
There are instances where Lear requests personally identifiable information to provide the Web site visitor a service or correspondence (promotions and mailed brochures). This information, such as name, mailing address, email address, type of request and possibly additional information, is collected and stored in a manner appropriate to the nature of the data by Lear and is used to fulfill your request. If you tell us that the information should not be used as a basis for further contact, we will respect your request. The information you provide is used by Lear to improve the services we provide you. It is never provided to any other company for that company's independent use.
E-mail / Contact Form that Contains Personal Information
Internet users may decide to send Lear personally identifying information, for example, in a message containing information about your Lear product or service or by contacting Lear using the contact form provided on the website. Lear will only use this information to identify the user as a customer and to determine how to respond to the electronic mail or the contact request via the contact form. We will not use this information other than to resolve the matter identified in the e-mail. We will delete the data stored in connection with your contact request as soon as it is no longer necessary for processing your request. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy. A revised Privacy Policy will only apply to data collected subsequent to its effective date. Any revisions will be posted at least 10 days prior to its effective date.
Use of Cookies
Lear uses cookies on the Web site. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer or mobile device by the Web sites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make Web sites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site. If you are uncomfortable with the use of cookies, you can manage and control them through your browser, including removing cookies by deleting them from your cache when you leave the site.
Lear uses Google Analytics to analyze and regularly improve the use of our Web site. The cookies used by Google Analytics provide information on how visitors use our Web site. The information collected includes the number of visitors to the site, where they came from and what pages they visited.
Lear also uses service cookies that help us to make our Web site work as efficiently as possible by remembering your Content ID or User token.
Use of Tracking Pixels
Lear uses Facebook tracking pixels and LinkedIn tracking pixels allowing users of the Web site to see interest-based advertisements when visiting the social networks Facebook or LinkedIn. The Facebook and LinkedIn pixels are integrated directly by Facebook respectively LinkedIn when you visit our Web site and can store a cookie on your device. If you then log in to Facebook or LinkedIn or visit those sites when logged in, the visit to our Web site will be recorded in your profile. We do not process any information to Facebook or LinkedIn allowing you to be identified directly. However, Facebook respectively LinkedIn stores and processes the data so that a connection to your user profile is possible.
By using our Web Site, you agree that we can place these tracking pixels on your device.
Social Media Plug-Ins
Lear uses the following social media plug-ins: Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter, Instagram, Youtube. These social media plug-ins enable direct communication between your device and the servers of the social network providers. Data will be transmitted to these social networks only if you actively click on the respective social media icon. In this case, your web browser starts a connection to the respective social network’s servers. By clicking on the social media icon you agree that your browser will produce a link to the respective social network’s servers and transmit usage data to the respective operator of the social network and vice versa. Lear has no influence upon the nature and extent of the data that is then gathered by the social networks.
Your Rights and How to Exercise Them
Under certain circumstances, you have rights under data protection laws in relation to your Personal Data. These rights can be exercised by contacting Lear and may include the right of access to and rectification or erasure of Personal Data, to restrict the processing of Personal Data as well as the right to data portability, the right to withdraw consent at any time (where Lear processes Personal Data based on consent) and the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.
Home
CompanyOverviewHistoryVision & ValuesLeadershipNewsroomCOVID-19 UpdatesIdea PortalResourcesLear Student Innovation ChallengeTechnologyOverviewSeatingE-SystemsINTU™Lear ConnexUs™Crafted by Lear™ImpACTConfigurE+TrendsOverviewConnectivityElectrificationMobilityCraftsmanshipESGOverviewMessage from our CEOEnvironmentOperation GIVEAwardsGreen TechnologyFocus On The DriveInvestorsOverviewEarnings ReleasesEvents / PresentationsCorporate GovernanceFinancial InformationSEC FillingsStock InformationAnalyst CoverageContactShareholder ToolsSuppliersOverviewSupplier DiversitySupplier Sustainability PolicyPO Terms & ConditionsConflict MineralsHuman Rights & Forced LaborWeb ApplicationsWeb GuidesEDI GuidelinesAffiliatesCorporate GovernanceCareersOverviewJob OpeningsOur CultureDiversity & InclusionEmployee SpotlightsContactContact FormGlobal Locations
Corporate HQ
21557 Telegraph Road
Southfield, MI 48033
248.447.1500
Back To Top
